const cppQuestions = [
  {
    question: 'Choose the operator which cannot be overloaded',
    a: '/',
    b: '()',
    c: '::',
    d: '%',
    answer: 'c',
  },
  {
    question: 'The pointer which stores always the current active object address is __',
    a: 'auto_ptr',
    b: 'this',
    c: 'p',
    d: 'self',
    answer: 'b',
  },
  {
    question: 'HAS-A relationship between the classes is shown through',
    a: 'Inheritance',
    b: 'Container classes',
    c: 'Polymorphism',
    d: 'Abstraction',
    answer: 'b',
  },
  {
    question: 'An exception is __',
    a: 'Runtime Error',
    b: 'Compile Time Error',
    c: 'Logical Error',
    d: 'Execution Error',
    answer: 'a',
  },
  {
    question: 'Where does the object is created?',
    a: 'class',
    b: 'constructor',
    c: 'destructor',
    d: 'attributes',
    answer: 'a',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these following members are not accessed by using direct member access operator?',
    a: 'public',
    b: 'private',
    c: 'protected',
    d: 'public and protected',
    answer: 'd',
  },
  {
    question: "Pick out the other definition of objects.",
    a: 'member of the class',
    b: 'associate of the class',
    c: 'attribute of the class',
    d: 'instance of the class',
    answer: 'd',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following function / types of function cannot have default parameters?',
    a:
      'Member function of class',
    b:
      'main()',
    c: 'Member function of structure',
    d: 'Recursive Function',
    answer: 'b',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is symbol for writing a comment in C++?',
    a: '//',
    b: '#',
    c: '--',
    d: '~',
    answer: 'a',
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following function / type of function cannot be overloaded?",
    a: 'Member Function',
    b: 'Static Function',
    c: 'Virtual Function',
    d: 'Recursive Function',
    answer: 'c',
  },
]

export default cppQuestions
